[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- Presenting Dicky's double surprise... meatloaf.
——介绍迪基的双重惊喜...肉饼。
- That's a chicken.
——那是只鸡。
- Surprise!
——惊喜！
- [coughs] That tastes like meatloaf.
——[咳嗽]这味道像肉饼。
- Double surprise!
——双重惊喜！
- Why did we let him cook again?
——我们为什么又让他做饭了？
- So, while this cools, how's school going?
——那么，在它冷却的时候，学校怎么样？
You guys excited about graduating?
你们对毕业感到兴奋吗？
- Oh, well, graduation's cool and all,
——哦，毕业当然很酷，
but we are way more psyched about our Sayonara Stunt.
但我们对我们的‘告别特技’更加兴奋。
- The outgoing class does a stunt at the end
- 毕业班在学年末表演一个特技，
of the school year so their legacy will be remembered.
以便他们的传统能被记住。
- Oh, we know what a Sayonara Stunt is.
- 哦，我们知道什么是‘告别特技’。
- We invented that term 30 years ago
- 我们30年前创造了这个术语，
when we were on the Stunt Committee at Edgewood.
当时我们在Edgewood的特技委员会。
- Wait, no way! We're on that Stunt Committee, too!
- 等等，不可能！我们也在那个特技委员会！
- Oh, that's fantastic! - Oh, how cool!
- 哦，那太棒了！ - 哦，真酷！
- We're so excited! Our first meeting is tonight
- 我们太兴奋了！我们的第一次会议是今晚
and we wanna do something awesome.
而且我们想做点很棒的事情。
Like the Butt Bench.
比如Butt Bench。
- See, a long time ago, the school had just put
你看，很久以前，学校刚刚在前入口处
a new concrete bench in the front entryway.
安装了一个新的混凝土长椅。
- Then, two anonymous kids left their butt prints
然后，两个匿名的孩子就在湿水泥上
in the wet cement. - And they've been there
留下了他们的臀部印记。
ever since. - Oh, we know
从那以后就一直留在那里了。
what the Butt Bench is.
哦，我们知道Butt Bench是什么。
In fact, does this ring a bell?
实际上，这个听起来有印象吗？
Ding-a-ling-a-ling.
叮-铃-铃。
- That's right. You guys, our behinds
没错。你们，我们的臀部
are the behinds left behind on the Butt Bench.
是那些被留在Butt Bench上的屁股。
[gasping] - [laughs]
[倒吸一口气] - [笑]
- You guys are legends.
- 你们真是传奇。
How come you never told us before?
为什么你们之前从没告诉我们？
- Oh, we didn't tell anybody.
- 哦，我们没告诉任何人。
Not everyone approved of the stunt.
不是每个人都赞成这个特技。
- You have no idea how hard it's been,
- 你们不知道这有多难，
keeping it to ourselves. - [laughs]
保守这个秘密。 - [笑]
- It's like a crushing weight on our chest.
- 这就像压在我们胸口的沉重负担。
I mean, it's so good to finally tell someone.
我是说，终于能告诉别人真是太好了。
But don't tell anyone!
但别告诉任何人！
- Wow, I hope our stunt can last as long as yours did.
- 哇，我希望我们的恶作剧能像你们的一样持久。
- Aw, thanks, honey. It warms my heart to know
- 哦，谢谢，亲爱的。知道我们的最大臀肌给你们的生活留下了深刻印象，我感到很温暖。
that our gluteus made maximus impressions on your lives.
- 哦，不，这是个好笑话。 - 对吧？
- Oh, no, that's a good one. - Right?
[笑声]
[laughter]
- 嗯，很遗憾他们要把它移走。
- Well, it's too bad they're getting rid of it.
- 长椅？什么？为什么？
- The bench? What? Why?
- 他们下周要重新装修学校的整个前部，长椅是第一个要移走的东西。
- Well, they're remodeling the whole front of the school
- 显然，它是个健康隐患。
next week and the bench is the first thing to go.
每次下雨，臀部的积水都会引来蚊子。
- Apparently, it's a health hazard.
显然，它是个健康隐患。
Every time it rains, the butt puddles bring mosquitoes.
每次下雨，那些屁股水坑就会引来蚊子。
- No, they can't just destroy history.
不，他们不能就这样毁掉历史。
I won't stand for it. - You'll have to, Anne.
我不会容忍这种事。
There'll be no bench. - Oh, well,
你得接受现实，安妮。
the School Beautification Board is meeting tonight.
那条长椅将不复存在。
You can go and see if you can change their minds.
哦，对了，
- Yeah, and give us a ride to our meeting.
学校美化委员会今晚开会。
We've got a Sayonara Stunt of our own to plan.
你可以去看看能否改变他们的主意。
- Okay, but first, Dicky worked very hard on a nice meal for us.
好的，但首先，迪基为我们精心准备了一顿美餐。
So let's eat. - Thanks, Mom.
那我们开动吧。 - 谢谢妈妈。
Bone apple teeth, everybody.
祝大家用餐愉快。
- It's bon appétit.
- 是bon appétit。
- No. Bone, apple, teeth.
- 不对。是bone, apple, teeth。
It's all in there.
全都在里面了。
- Or we could just go now.
- 或者我们现在就走。
- Yeah, let's go. - Let's...yeah, yeah.
- 对，走吧。 - 走吧...对，对。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪♪
- There it is. - Hm.
- 在那儿。 - 嗯。
- The Butt Bench. - We have to
- 屁股凳。 - 我们必须
save our legacy, Tom. [mosquitoes buzzing]
保护我们的遗产，汤姆。 [蚊子嗡嗡声]
- Hopefully ours won't attract as many mosquitoes.
- 希望我们的不会吸引这么多蚊子。
- Run!
- 跑！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
- This is it. For the rest of our lives,
这就是了。对我们余生而言，
we'll remember this as the night we planned history.
我们将记住这一晚，我们计划历史的夜晚。
- I'll remember it as the night I left the house
我会记住这一晚，我离家时没穿内裤。
without my underwear on.
你没穿内裤？
- You don't have underwear on?
哦。[嗤笑]我穿了。
- Oh. [scoffs] I do.
只是不是我的。
Just not mine.
不重要。除非是你的。
- Not important. Unless it's mine.
是你的吗？我不想知道。
Is it mine? I don't wanna know.
是的，我穿了。不，我没穿。
Yes, I do. No, I don't.
是的，我有。不，我没有。
Let's just focus on coming up with a stunt
我们还是专注于想出一个能给那些家伙好看的花招吧。
that sticks it to the man.
是我的吗？
Is it mine?
是我的。
It's mine.
好了，同学们，我们开始开会吧。
- All right, students. Let's get this meeting started.
等等，塔里安校长在这里做什么？
- Wait, what's Principal Tarian doing here?
我以为娜特莉是负责人。
I thought Natlee was in charge.
他在监督委员会。
- He's overseeing the committee.
现在，我知道你们都很兴奋。
- Now, I know you're all excited.
我当年坐在这个房间里，也是同样兴奋，计划着我们班的告别恶作剧。
I was, too, when I sat in this very room all those years ago
我当年坐在这个房间里的时候也是这样，
and planned my class' Sayonara Stunt.
策划了我们班级的告别恶作剧。
[chuckles] Ah.
[轻笑] 啊。
The infamous immense signature of '87.
那著名的'87年级的巨大签名。
Who doesn't remember that one, huh?
谁不记得那个呢，嗯？
[all disagreeing]
[大家都不同意]
- Of course, you all know it as the Butt Bench.
- 当然，你们都知道它叫做屁股凳。
[all agreeing]
[大家都同意]
- Well, it wasn't always the Butt Bench.
- 其实，它并不总是叫屁股凳。
First, I wrote "Class of '87" in the cement
起初，我在水泥上写下了'87年级'的字样
and it was beautiful.
而且它很美。
Until two anonymous hooligans sat on it
直到两个匿名的捣蛋鬼坐了上去
and wiped out our classy class legacy
抹去了我们班级的优雅传承
with their felonious tushies.
用他们犯罪的小屁股。
- Did you ever figure out who was behind it?
- 你查出是谁干的了吗？
[laughter] - Yeah, did you ever
[笑声] - 是啊，你查清楚了没？
get to the bottom of it?
- 找到问题的根源了吗？
- No.
- 没有。
- So you never cracked the case?
- 那你一直没有破案？
- Ah, you must be really bummed.
- 啊，你一定很沮丧。
- This is exactly what I don't like about the Butt Bench!
这正是我不喜欢臀部凳的原因！
And so this year's stunt doesn't get out of hand like that one,
所以为了避免今年的恶作剧像上次那样失控，
I'm providing you with a list of approved stunts to choose from.
我提供了一份经批准的恶作剧清单供你们选择。
- Wait, what? This is lame.
等等，什么？这太逊了。
All of us wearing buttons to the dedication ceremony
我们所有人穿着纽扣去参加落成典礼，
that says "Class of '17."
上面写着'17级班级'。
How is that even a stunt?
这怎么能算恶作剧呢？
- [laughs]
（笑）
You'll be wearing them...
你们会倒着戴...
[laughs]
（笑）
Upside down.
倒过来。
- I was thinking more like
- 我原本想的是
when you're making your speech,
当你发表演讲时，
we slowly lower a wig on your head.
我们慢慢在你的头上放一顶假发。
- No.
- 不行。
- Okay, I don't think you heard the slowly part.
- 好吧，我觉得你没听到'慢慢'这个词。
- I did.
- 我听到了。
- Did you hear the wig part?
- 那你听到'假发'这个词了吗？
- Pick off the Sayonara Stunt list,
- 从'告别特技'清单上划掉，
or you will all be saying, "Konnichiwa" to summer school.
否则你们都得说'你好'去上暑期学校。
That's Japanese for "hello."
那是日语中的“你好”。
Good-bye.
再见。
Which is English for "sayonara."
这是英语中的“再见”。
I'm leaving.
我要走了。
- Okay, everyone, take a look at the list.
好吧，大家，看看这个列表。
- We're not really gonna pick off this list, are we?
我们不会真的要完成这个列表吧，是吗？
- [scoffs] I don't wanna go to summer school.
（嗤之以鼻）我不想去上暑期学校。
- Summer school? So not cool.
暑期学校？太不酷了。
- Some of this stuff isn't so bad.
其中一些事情并不那么糟糕。
- Upside down buttons?
倒挂的按钮？
Adopting a dove and naming it Principal Taradove?
领养一只鸽子并给它取名叫校长塔拉鸽？
Come on! This is your chance
拜托！这是你的机会
to leave an unforgettable legacy.
留下一个难忘的遗产。
How do you want to be remembered?
你希望如何被记住？
- As a kid who didn't have to go to summer school.
- 作为一个不需要去上暑期学校的孩子。
[together] Zip it, Franco!
[一起] 闭嘴，弗兰科！
- Dawn's right, we have one shot at doing something historic.
- 黎明说得对，我们有一次做些历史性事情的机会。
- So what'll it be?
- 那么，你选什么？
This forgettable list or immortality?
这份容易被遗忘的清单还是永垂不朽？
all: Forgettable list.
所有人: 容易被遗忘的清单。
[together] What?
[together] 什么？
- You know, I think the quads are right.
- 你知道吗，我觉得四胞胎说得对。
all: What?
all: 什么？
- We need to go big.
- 我们需要大干一场。
And I think the quad should be in charge of planning it.
而且我认为应该由四胞胎来负责策划。
After all, who's better at going big than them?
毕竟，还有谁能比他们更擅长做大事情呢？
- She has a point.
- 她说得有道理。
- So here's my plan.
- 那么，这是我的计划。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Wow, I can't believe the Committee put us in charge
- 哇，真不敢相信委员会让我们负责
of our own super secret committee
负责我们自己的超级秘密委员会
to come up with a Sayonara Stunt.
来策划一场告别秀。
- It's a pretty big honor. - Yeah.
- 这是相当大的荣誉。 - 是啊。
All right. So anybody got any ideas?
好吧。那谁有什么想法吗？
- Ooh! - Besides a slow wig drop?
- 哦！ - 除了慢慢放下假发之外？
- Imagine this is the wig.
- 想象这就是假发。
- Anything else?
- 还有别的吗？
- I got nothing. - Me neither.
- 我什么也想不出来。 - 我也是。
- Drawing a blank.
- 一片空白。
- Why can't we think of anything?
- 我们怎么什么也想不出来？
- I know. We don't have Chinese food.
我知道，我们没有中餐。
- Chinese food?
中餐？
- Yeah. Whenever they have to
是的，每当他们在电影中需要想点什么的时候，
think of something in movies,
他们总是点中餐，
they always get Chinese food
然后直接从盒子里拿出来吃。
and eat it right out of the box.
没错，他说的没错。
- Yeah, he's not wrong.
宇航员被困在火星上？
Astronaut stuck on Mars?
没有任务控制中心点的鸡肉炒面，他是不会回来的。
He's not coming back without Mission Control
让我们把那位英雄带回家。
ordering up some chicken chow mein.
哇，Dicky，我突然感觉
- Let's bring that hero home.
- 让我们把那位英雄带回家。
- Wow, Dicky, I'm suddenly feeling
- 哇，迪基，我突然感到
a flurry of ideas coming on.
一阵灵感涌上心头。
- That billboard on Main, right?
- 就是主街上的那个广告牌，对吧？
- That's a good idea. - And we'll just do--
- 那是个好主意。 - 我们就这么做——
Oh, hey, kids. I guess we'll have to
哦，嘿，孩子们。我想我们得
find a different classroom. - Yeah.
找个不同的教室。 - 是啊。
- Wait, why do you guys need a classroom?
- 等等，你们为什么需要一个教室？
- Oh, you know, for some very important stuff.
- 哦，你知道的，为了一些非常重要的事情。
- We were fighting to save the Butt Bench.
- 我们当时在为保护屁股长椅而战。
And it seemed like everyone was against us.
而且好像每个人都反对我们。
But then, all of a sudden, Principal Tarian picked us
但突然之间，塔里安校长选了我们
to form a super secret committee
组成一个超级秘密委员会
to figure out how to save it.
来找出如何拯救它的方法。
- It's a pretty big honor.
- 这是一个相当大的荣誉。
- Oh, yeah. - Wait, so Principal Tarian
- 哦，是的。 - 等等，所以塔里安校长
just suddenly changed everyone's minds?
突然改变了所有人的想法？
- And put you two in charge of a super secret committee?
- 并让你们两个负责一个超级秘密委员会？
- Doesn't that seem a little fishy?
- 这听起来不是很可疑吗？
Like, maybe he was just trying to get rid of you.
就像，也许他只是想摆脱你们。
- Looks like you guys got played.
看起来你们被耍了。
both: Oh.
哦。
- Well, what are you guys doing in here?
那么，你们在这里做什么？
- Oh, well, we are working on real very important stuff.
哦，我们在忙一些非常重要的事情。
- We were fighting to change the Sayonara Stunt.
我们当时在努力改变告别特技。
- It seemed like everyone was against us.
好像每个人都反对我们。
- Then, suddenly, Natlee changed her mind.
然后，突然间，Natlee改变了主意。
- Oh, and sent you in here to form
哦，然后派你们来这里组建
a super secret committee?
一个超级秘密委员会？
[together] Yeah!
是的！
Ohh.
哦。
- They did trick us.
他们确实骗了我们。
- Well, I mean, I'm sure it's just a misunderstanding.
嗯，我的意思是，我确信这只是个误会。
I mean, Mae would never trick us.
我是说，Mae绝不会骗我们。
I'll just go in there and ask her what's up.
我这就进去问问她怎么回事。
- If they didn't trick us, then why is the door locked?
如果他们没骗我们，那为什么门是锁着的？
- Oh, well, just 'cause the door's locked
哦，好吧，只是因为门锁了
doesn't mean that they meant--
并不意味着他们有意——
Just 'cause they closed the blinds on us
只是因为他们把百叶窗关上了
doesn't mean that they meant to trick--
并不意味着他们有意要骗——
- Sorry.
对不起。
- Just 'cause Mae opened the blinds and mouthed "sorry"
只是因为Mae打开百叶窗并嘴型说了'对不起'
doesn't mean that they mean to--
并不意味着他们有意...
all: Go away!
走开！
- Yeah, they tricked us. - Yeah.
是的，他们骗了我们。
[upbeat music]
是的。
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
啦啦啦啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦啦
- This is so not cool! Mae won't even answer my texts.
这太不酷了！Mae甚至不回我短信。
- I don't get it. Why would they wanna plan
我不明白。他们为什么要计划
the Sayonara Stunt without us?
没有我们的告别特技？
- I don't know, but we have to find out.
- 我不知道，但我们必须弄清楚。
- Well, if we wait a little bit, we can just ask them.
- 好吧，如果我们稍等一会儿，就可以直接问他们。
Chinese food makes you thirsty,
中餐会让你口渴，
so eventually, they'll have to come out for water.
所以他们最终会不得不出来找水喝。
- Wait, I thought turkey makes you thirsty.
- 等等，我以为火鸡会让你口渴。
- No, turkey makes you sleepy.
- 不，火鸡会让你犯困。
- Oh. Oh.
- 哦。哦。
I bet I could kick a turkey's butt.
我敢打赌我能踢火鸡的屁股。
- Why would you wanna kick a turkey's butt?
- 你为什么要踢火鸡的屁股？
- I don't. I'm just saying I could.
- 我没有这个打算。我只是说我能做到。
- No way. Do you know how big turkeys are?
不可能。你知道火鸡有多大吗？
Oh, and they're mean, too.
哦，而且它们还很凶。
- Yeah, a turkey would destroy you.
是啊，火鸡会把你打得落花流水。
- No. Dicky's the destroyer.
不。迪基才是那个破坏者。
- You'd have zero chance.
你一点机会都没有。
- Come on, I'd just grab his little gobbler like this.
来吧，我只要这样抓住它的小脖子。
Then I'd sweep his legs and take him to the ground.
然后我扫它的腿，把它放倒。
That's right, turkey. Stay down!
没错，火鸡。乖乖躺下！
See?
看到了吗？
- Sure, it's easy when your imaginary turkey's
当然，当你想象中的火鸡不还手时，这很容易。
not fighting back.
不还手。
Now try. Gobble! Gobble!
现在试试。咯咯！咯咯！
Gobble, gobble! - Ow! That hurts!
咯咯，咯咯！ - 哎哟！那很疼！
- Wait, guys, can we not? Can we not?
- 等等，伙计们，我们能不能不这样？能不能不这样？
Like, we're in the middle of a meeting, seriously.
就像，我们正在开会，说真的。
Guys, stop, stop! - Whoa, whoa!
伙计们，停下，停下！ - 哇，哇！
- Guys, guys! Time out on the fake turkey fight!
- 伙计们，伙计们！假火鸡打架暂停！
The Committee's gone. - [sighs]
委员会已经走了。 - [叹气]
- Great. Now how are we gonna find out
- 太好了。现在我们怎么才能弄清楚
why they didn't want us to be part of the stunt?
他们为什么不想让我们参与特技表演？
- We'll figure something out.
- 我们会想出办法的。
But first...time in! - No!
但首先...继续！ - 不！
- Gobble, gobble, gobble! - Ow! That seriously hurts!
- 咯咯，咯咯，咯咯！ - 噢！那真的很痛！
- That's right, Dicky! Stay down!
- 没错，迪基！别起来！
That'll teach him to wear my underwear.
这会让他记住别穿我的内裤。
♪ ♪
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
- ♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
[knock at door] - Okay, that's Mae.
[敲门声] - 好了，那是梅。
Everyone just stick to the plan and we'll get her to talk.
大家按照计划行事，我们会让她开口的。
both: Hey, guys.
两人: 嘿，伙计们。
- Oh, you brought Miles.
- 哦，你把迈尔斯带来了。
- Yeah. Is that a problem?
- 是的。这有问题吗？
- Yeah, we don't have a plan for him.
- 是的，我们没有针对他的计划。
- Ah, dut, dut, dut, dut, duh.
- 啊，这个那个那个。
What he means is we just don't
他的意思是，我们只是没有
have enough pie for everybody.
足够的派给每个人。
Hey, come on. [laughs]
嘿，来吧。[笑]
Keep him busy.
让他忙起来。
- So...
- 所以...
you think I could take a turkey?
你觉得我可以拿一只火鸡吗？
- Have a seat, Mae.
- 坐下，Mae。
Oh, look.
哦，看。
Got your favorite pie.
有你最喜欢的派。
Key lime. - Oh, thanks!
酸橙派。 - 哦，谢谢！
- Yeah, that key lime's nice, isn't it?
- 是啊，那个酸橙派不错，对吧？
- Mm-hmm. - Underrated pie,
- 嗯哼。 - 如果问我的话，这是被低估的派。
if you ask me.
关于委员会的事，
So about the committee,
你知道我们为什么被锁在外面吗？
you have any idea why we got locked out?
- 我不太方便回答这个问题。
- I'm not comfortable answering that question.
对不起。 - [叹气]
I'm sorry. - [sighs]
对不起。
I'm sorry too, Mae.
我也对不起，Mae。
Dawn tried to be nice.
Dawn试图表现得友好。
But nice time is over.
但友好时光已经结束了。
- [laughs] You know I'm afraid of balloons.
你知道我害怕气球。
- Oh, I know, sweetheart.
哦，我知道，亲爱的。
- Stay down, turkey!
趴下，火鸡！
See?
看？
[balloon stretching]
我在听谁在扭气球吗？
- Am I hearing someone twist a balloon?
嗯，我想你听到的声音是我扭这只火鸡脖子的声音。
- Uh, I think what you're hearing
嗯，我想你听到的是
is the sound of me twisting this turkey's neck.
我扭断这只火鸡脖子的声音。
[imitates twisting]
（模仿扭动声）
- Mae, just talk and the balloon turkey goes away.
Mae，只要说话，气球火鸡就会消失。
- I'm sorry. I can't talk about it.
对不起，我不能谈论这件事。
- [sighs] Wrong choice, kitten.
（叹气）错误的选择，小猫。
[balloon pops] - Aah!
（气球爆裂声）啊！
- Was that Mae?
那是Mae吗？
- No. [laughs] - I didn't hear anything.
不。（笑）我什么都没听到。
[balloon pops] - Aah!
（气球爆裂声）啊！
- I didn't hear that either.
我也没听到。
- What's going on in here?
这里发生了什么？
And why are you holding a balloon turkey in Mae's face?
还有，你为什么拿着一个气球火鸡在Mae面前？
And what's with this family and turkeys?
还有，这个家庭和火鸡有什么关系？
- They're trying to get me to tell them
他们试图让我告诉他们
why they got kicked off the committee.
为什么他们被踢出了委员会。
- And I almost got her to sing.
我差点让她唱歌了。
Isn't that right, doll face?
对吧，娃娃脸？
- This is ridiculous.
这太荒谬了。
Look, I didn't wanna hurt your feelings,
听着，我不想伤害你的感情，
but the committee didn't want you guys
但是委员会不希望你们参与这个特技，因为你们总是...
to be part of the stunt because you always...
- 什么？ - 直说吧。
- What? - Just say it.
- 总是把事情搞砸！
- Quad things up!
- 把事情搞砸？这是什么意思？
- Quad things up? What's that supposed to mean?
- 当你们四个人参与进来时，
- When the four of you guys get involved,
事情迟早会失控。
sooner or later, things get out of hand.
- 然后完全搞砸。
- And totally messed up.
- [嗤之以鼻] - 你在说什么？
- [scoffs] - What are you talking about?
- 就像昨天，你们在等委员会出来时，
- Like yesterday, when you were waiting
但你们却开始争吵，
for the committee to come out,
等待委员会出来，
but instead you started arguing,
但你却开始争吵，
so everyone just snuck out behind you.
结果大家都偷偷从你背后溜走了。
- And that right there is quadding it up.
这就是你们四个一起搞砸事情的典型。
together: Ohh.
哦。
- Well, quadding it up or not,
不管是不是一起搞砸，
everyone agrees, I could definitely kick a turkey's butt.
大家都同意，我绝对能踢飞一只火鸡。
- Any turkey on Earth-- wild, domesticated, or frozen--
任何地球上的火鸡——野生的、家养的，还是冷冻的——
would wreck you.
都能把你打趴下。
- I'd take any turkey.
我随便挑一只火鸡都行。
- You couldn't even take a balloon turkey.
- 你连气球火鸡都打不过。
- Oh! Ow. - Again, why do you even
- 哦！哎呀。- 再说一次，你为什么想和火鸡打架？
want to fight a turkey? - I don't,
- 我并不想，
but what choice do I have?
但我有什么选择？
- Gobble, gobble, gobble!
- 咕咕咕！
- Leave him alone. - Ow.
- 别理他了。- 哎哟。
[door closes] - Uh, guys?
[门关上] - 呃，伙计们？
They're gone.
他们走了。
- Maybe we do quad things up.
- 也许我们真的应该一起做点事。
- We were so caught up about doing something big
- 我们太沉迷于为班级留下重大事迹，以至于都没意识到班上同学实际上对我们的看法。
for the class' legacy, we didn't even realize
为了班级的传统，我们甚至没有意识到
what the class actually thinks of us.
班级实际上是怎么看待我们的。
- Yeah, our legacy is all quadded up.
- 是的，我们的传统全都搞砸了。
- [sighs] - How did we end up like this?
- [叹气] - 我们怎么会变成这样？
[both laughing] We got Shelly!
[两人笑] 我们得到了Shelly！
- Yeah, and if Principal Tarian wants her back,
- 是的，如果Tarian校长想要她回来，
he's gotta save that bench.
他得先保住那条长椅。
- Uh...that's not Shelly.
- 呃...那不是Shelly。
- You really Tommed this up.
- 你真的把这事搞砸了，Tom。
- What's that supposed to mean, Anne?
- 那是什么意思，Anne？
- That explains it. - Yeah.
这就解释得通了。
♪ ♪
是的。
- Sorry we're late. [laughs]
对不起，我们迟到了。[笑]
- Um, what are you guys doing here?
呃，你们在这里做什么？
- Look, we know you don't want us to be part of the stunt.
看，我们知道你不想让我们参与这个特技。
You think we'll just quad it up. - But we're here to prove
你认为我们会只是四人一组。
that our quadding it up is a thing of the past.
但我们来这里是为了证明
From now on, we're gonna be team players.
我们的四人组已经是过去式了。
- And we're also going to beg.
从现在开始，我们要成为团队的一员。
[together] Please! [overlapping begging]
我们还会恳求。
- We promise we won't do anything wrong!
- 我们保证不会做错事！
- You swar? [together] We swar.
- 你发誓？[一起] 我们发誓。
- Fine, you're back in - Yeah!
- 好吧，你们回来了 - 耶！
- Okay, here's the plan:
- 好的，计划是这样的：
when they take out the Butt Bench,
当他们移走那张屁股凳时，
they have to repave the entryway.
他们得重新铺设入口。
We're gonna write "2017" in that fresh, new cement.
我们将在那新鲜的水泥上写上“2017”。
- Ooh, nice. - Yeah, okay.
- 哦，不错。 - 是的，好的。
- Unzip it, Franco. Show 'em the diagram.
- 拉开拉链，弗兰科。给他们看看图纸。
all: Ooh!
所有人: 哦！
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
all: Ahh!
Ahh!
- The Sayonara Stunt is complete.
- 告别特技完成了。
What do you think?
你觉得怎么样？
- This stunt is officially principal-approved.
- 这个特技已经正式得到校长的批准。
- This is the lamest stunt ever.
- 这是最无聊的特技。
- We should fix this.
- 我们应该改进这个。
No. We always quad it up.
不，我们总是四人一组。
I should fix this.
我应该修复这个。
- If I fix this myself, there's no chance
- 如果我自己修复这个，就没有机会
it'd be quadded up.
它会被四倍放大。
- I can save the class legacy
- 我可以拯救班级传统
without ruining the quad's legacy.
而不破坏四人组的传承。
- I've gotta fix this.
- 我必须修复这个。
Time to Ricky it up.
是时候里基风格了。
- Time to Dicky it up.
- 是时候迪基风格了。
- Time to Nicky it up.
- 是时候尼基风格了。
- Time to get her Dawn.
- 是时候让她黎明了。
- Why do you guys all look like
为什么你们看起来都像是在心里默念什么？
you're saying stuff in your head?
我们没有。
- No we don't. - What? Us?
什么？我们？
- It's preposterous.
这太荒谬了。
- You're still doing it.
你们还在做。
- What? - Us?
什么？我们？
- No way! - Hippopotamus.
不可能！
Nailed it.
河马。
[upbeat music]
说中了。
- Perfect.
完美。
- Hey. What are you doing here?
嘿，你在这里做什么？
- What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
- What are either of you doing here?
你们俩在这里做什么？
[thud]
[砰]
- What am I doing here?
我在这里做什么？
- First thing's first.
首先第一件事。
Dawn, what were you doing under that tarp?
Dawn，你在那块防水布下面做什么？
- I saved the class' legacy.
我保护了班级的遗产。
Well...what do you think?
那么...你觉得怎么样？
- I think you've done an excellent job...
我认为你做得非常出色...
of betraying me.
背叛了我。
- And me.
- 还有我。
- I fell out of a tree.
- 我从树上掉下来了。
- What are you talking about?
- 你在说什么？
- Uh, I was in a tree and I fell.
- 呃，我在树上，然后掉下来了。
- No. I saved the class' legacy
- 不。我保护了班级的遗产
without ruining the quad's legacy.
没有破坏广场的遗产。
You're welcome. - Oh, so that's why
不用谢。 - 哦，所以这就是为什么
you came out here alone.
你一个人来这里。
You thought we'd quad it up.
你以为我们会一起行动。
- Well, why did you come out here alone?
- 那你为什么一个人出来？
- Don't change the subject.
- 别转移话题。
- I can't believe you thought I would quad it up.
- 真不敢相信你以为我会四人组队。
You're the one who quads things up more than anybody.
你才是那个比谁都爱组队的人。
Like right now!
就像现在这样！
Your two looks like a seven.
你的两个看起来像七个。
Now give me that stick and let me fix it.
现在把那根棍子给我，让我来修。
- No! Stop! - No, let me fix it.
- 不！住手！ - 不，让我来修。
Your twos aren't any better.
你的两个也没好到哪儿去。
- No, let me do it.
- 不，让我来弄。
- My twos are excellent. What are you talking about?
- 我的二点看起来很棒。你在说什么呢？
- No, they're not! - You guys are just
- 不，它们不行！ - 你们只会
gonna mess it up, I was here first!
把它搞砸，我先来的！
[overlapping argument]
[重叠的争吵]
Guys, guys, guys!
伙计们，伙计们，伙计们！
- [sighs] - Look.
- [叹气] - 看。
- Looks like we quadded it up again.
- 看起来我们又搞砸了。
- Well, not yet. I mean, we still have time
- 还没呢。我是说，我们还有时间
before the other classmates get here.
在其他同学到来之前。
We can just clear this up with some quick dry cement.
我们可以用快干水泥清理一下。
Here, Dicky, go grab the tools.
这里，Dicky，去拿工具。
- Uh-oh. I'm stuck.
哎呀，我卡住了。
- Me too!
我也是！
- It's the quick dry cement.
是快干水泥。
- Quick dry!
快干！
- Okay. Now we quadded it up.
好吧，这下我们真成了一伙了。
- What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办？
- Uh, let's just leave the shoes and go.
呃，我们把鞋留下，走吧。
[voices approaching] - Oh, too late.
（声音接近）哦，太晚了。
Here comes the Stunt Committee.
特技委员会来了。
- Quick, the tarps!
- Hey, guys. You're here early.
- Yep. - Super early!
- Getting that worm.
- We're not stuck in the cement. [laughs]
- Why is the tarp all messed up?
- Uh...
There, all better.
- Yeah, but that side's messed up, too.
- Fix it!
Really?
真的吗？
- Something's not right.
有什么不对劲。
I knew it! You quadded it up.
我就知道！你们搞砸了。
- Us? [laughs]
我们？[笑]
Why would you assume it's us?
你为什么会认为是我们的错？
- Because it's always you.
因为总是你们。
- And because your feet are stuck in the cement.
而且因为你们的脚陷在水泥里。
- Those are two excellent arguments.
这两个理由都很充分。
Help me!
帮帮我！
- How could you?
你怎么能这样？
- We're sorry. - But we couldn't let
- 我们很抱歉。- 但我们不能让
our class legacy be a weak, forgettable scribble.
我们的班级传统变得软弱无力，容易被遗忘。
- Scribble?
- 容易被遗忘？
Natlee has great penmanship.
Natlee的字迹非常漂亮。
- It's not about the "penmanshop."
- 这不仅仅是关于“书写技巧”。
- No, it's about you guys always messing everything up.
- 不，是你们总是把一切都搞砸。
- True, this wasn't our best day.
- 确实，今天不是我们表现最好的一天。
- But if you guys give us another chance,
- 但如果你们再给我们一次机会，
the super secret committee has a plan to fix this.
超级秘密委员会有一个计划来修复这一切。
- I hope she knows what she's doing.
- 我希望她知道自己在做什么。
- This better work.
这最好能行。
- I fell out of a tree.
我从树上摔下来了。
♪ ♪
- Today, I'm here to dedicate our school's new entryway.
今天，我来到这里是为了我们学校新入口的落成典礼。
But before I do, I present the class of 2017's Sayonara Stunt.
但在我这么做之前，我要展示2017届学生的告别特技。
Move, kids, so everyone can see
孩子们，让开点，让每个人都能看到
that adorable little inscription.
那个可爱的题词。
Why are you stepping out of your shoes?
你为什么脱掉鞋子？
What is the meaning of this?
这是什么意思？
- Sorry, Principal Tarian, but we just wanted
对不起，塔里安校长，但我们只是想
to pull off a stunt the whole class could call their own.
想搞个全班都能称之为自己的壮举。
- Something that actually represented us.
- 真正代表我们的事物。
- So we cemented our shoes into the ground.
- 所以我们把鞋子用水泥固定在地上了。
- I can only guess whose idea this was.
- 我只能猜这是谁的主意了。
This has Harper quads written all over it.
这肯定是哈珀四人组的主意。
- Um, actually, it has 2017 written all over it.
- 呃，实际上，这上面写着2017年。
- Oh, yeah, I see it now.
- 哦，对，我现在看到了。
- But it wasn't just the Harpers, it was all of us.
- 但不仅仅是哈珀们，是我们所有人。
We wanted to tell future classes that the class of 2017
我们想告诉未来的班级，2017届留下了一些相当大的鞋子要填补。
left some pretty big shoes to fill.
留下了一些相当大的鞋子要填补。
- Well, this wasn't on my list,
- 嗯，这不在我的清单上，
and it certainly wasn't principal-approved.
而且肯定也没有得到校长的批准。
But it is pretty inspired.
但这确实很有创意。
[all sighing]
[大家都叹气]
- Those are our kids, Tom. I've never been so proud.
- 那是我们的孩子，汤姆。我从未如此自豪。
- Our Butt Bench brought out the best of them.
- 我们的屁股长椅激发了他们最好的一面。
- Your Butt Bench?
- 你的屁股长椅？
- Ah, that's right, Arthur.
- 啊，没错，亚瑟。
The Butt Bench was brought to you by the Harper heinies.
屁股长椅是由哈珀家的屁股带来的。
- Ding-a-ling-a-ling!
- 叮-铃-铃！
- Ding-a-ling-a-ling?
叮-铃-铃？
- Thanks for making our Sayonara Stunt
感谢让我们的告别特技
way more memorable.
更加难忘。
- Maybe now our legacy won't be that we always quadded up.
也许现在我们的传奇不会只是我们总是四人一组。
- You're right.
你说得对。
This time, you were able to quad it up.
这次，你们能够四人一组了。
- What do you know? We were able to turn
你知道吗？我们成功地把
"quad it up" into a good thing.
‘四人一组’变成了好事。
- Good thing? Forget that.
好事？别提了。
My wig stunt it about to turn this into a great thing.
我的假发特技即将把这变成一件大事。
- Yes, you're just jealous.
- 是的，你就是嫉妒。
- What? Jealous? - Yes, jealous.
- 什么？嫉妒？ - 是的，嫉妒。
- Jealous? What?
- 嫉妒？什么？
[overlapping chatter]
[重叠的嘈杂声]
- Oh, what's so funny now? Huh?
- 哦，现在有什么好笑的？嗯？
Oh, now I'm funny, huh?
哦，现在我成了笑料，嗯？
- [gasps] - Oh!
- [喘气声] - 哦！
- There's a wig on my head, isn't there?
- 我头上有个假发，对吧？
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
[whistling]
♪ [口哨声] ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪